# **Anton Bojko**

Frontend developer

mrtoxas@gmail.com t.me/mrtoxas github.com/mrtoxas linkedin.com/in/mrtoxas

# **ABOUT ME**

Frontend developer with experience in creating web applications. I am proficient in various development tools and methodologies. I pay attention to design and optimization of projects, striving for perfect layouts and clean code. In my free time I study new technologies, read books and articles to expand my knowledge and skills.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

#### **KEY SKILLS:**

HTML, CSS, CSS/HTML preprocessors, JavaScript, TypeScript, jQuery, React, Vitepress, Astro, Vite, Webpack, Parcel, Gulp, Tailwind, UnoCSS, CSS Frameworks, ...

#### **FAMILIAR WITH:**

Node.js, Next.js, Vue, Prisma ORM, Python, PHP, Laravel, Docker, Wordpress, Figma, ...

# **EDUCATION**

## CHERKASY STATE TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY, MASTER'S DEGREE

2014-2018

- Computer systems and networks. Computer engineering
- Web programming courses (JavaScript, Ruby on Rails, Python), participation in elective classes provided by the university during the course of study

#### CHERKASY STATE BUSINESS COLLEGE, JUNIOR SPECIALIST

1998-2002

- Computer engineering Maintenance of computer and intellectual systems and networks
- The training program included the study of Assembler and Delphi programming languages

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER — FREELANCE

2022-2024

Working with regular clients. Development of full-stack solutions for small businesses.
 Technologies used: HTML/CSS/JS, Parcel, React, TypeScript, Vitepress, PHP, Laravel, Tailwind

#### FRONTEND-DEVELOPER — DIGITAL-AGENCY ONLY

2020-2022

- Participate in the development of enterprise projects, taking into account business requirements to ensure their functionality and efficiency.
- Support and further development of legacy projects.
- Actively participate in meetings and discussions on project requirements. Collaborating with other team members including designers, backend developers and project managers to solve problems.
- Experience leading development and design as a primary frontend developer on multiple projects.
  Technologies used: HTML/CSS/JS, React, TS, MobX, Ant Design, Styled Components, Vue, jQuery https://only.digital/

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER — FREELANCE

2017-2020

- Create lendings, corporate websites and other web solutions for businesses in a freelance web development team.
- Support, further development and problem solving in existing projects.
  Technologies used: HTML/CSS/JS, Gulp, SASS, WordPress, Python (Django)

# **SOCIAL ACTIVITY**

Since 2019, I have been actively participating in the professional web developer community on one of the popular online forums. I addressed issues related to web technologies and also served as a moderator, ensuring high-quality discussions and providing support for both newcomers and experienced developers.

Profile: https://www.cyberforum.ru/members/628162.html